{
    "id": "9bc34daa962244b4b1c23023c093a46b",
    "title": "Countable And Uncountable Nouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Could you pass me ……………………? I have spilled some juice on the floor.",
            "description": "A cloth is a piece of material used for cleaning.",
            "answers": [
                "a cloth",
                "a clothing",
                "a clothe"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "70cf672cb3b94815ac7bceca5ba61c72"
        },
        {
            "question": "I must buy ……………………………",
            "description": "Clothes does not have a singular form. We say a piece of clothing.",
            "answers": [
                "a clothing",
                "a clothe",
                "a piece of clothing"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f7ef8783e884414daba71776e68dca77"
        },
        {
            "question": "The poor man was arrested for stealing ………………………….",
            "description": "Bread is uncountable in English. The countable equivalents are a piece of bread / a loaf.",
            "answers": [
                "a bread",
                "a loaf"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1f551d24bb264d189d3fe542d9fc7fb5"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ………………………. money do you earn in a week?",
            "description": "Money is uncountable in English and hence it is used with much.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9a3d055c7f344460802ba1f4059d2640"
        },
        {
            "question": "A ………………………….. struck the building.",
            "description": "Lightning is uncountable. The countable equivalent is a flash of lightning.",
            "answers": [
                "lightning",
                "piece of lightning",
                "flash of lightning"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9ee2e383f27f46cba1f03604b63af23b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have got ………………………… to do.",
            "description": "Work is uncountable. ",
            "answers": [
                "much work",
                "many works"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fd94011721724287b7b8cf1c4c29887b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was held up by ………………………..",
            "description": "Traffic is uncountable. It does not have a plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "a traffic",
                "the traffic",
                "the traffics"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fc529614b56341f9b18f20b2b107ff50"
        },
        {
            "question": "Politics ………………………. a dirty game.",
            "description": "Politics is usually considered as a singular noun.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "65b56e015b5e49dead57019ee82840e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "In my opinion, too much mathematics ………………………. taught in schools.",
            "description": "Mathematics is usually considered as a singular noun.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "21e543a2109d4dab9be23b63fd047a57"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are all eager to increase our ……………………………",
            "description": "Knowledge does not have a plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "knowledge",
                "knowledges"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "835a5f5409e940aeb5bfcd27dbd448c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Six people lost their ……………………… in the accident.",
            "description": "To talk about several people doing the same thing or the same thing being done to several people, we normally use the plural form of the noun.",
            "answers": [
                "life",
                "lives"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4edce9e64f5d44bb814833e284fa95e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her ……………………….. very curly.",
            "description": "Hair is uncountable in English.",
            "answers": [
                "hair is",
                "hairs are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8b1cb701135c4552879ee3cb862a8992"
        }
    ]
}